[{"answer": "Can I take your order", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, right.  Here, see ya", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "She has a little brother on the way... we just did the ultrasound", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We are, Sky.  Very happy", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "you selling", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "A game", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The type", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'm not a player", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "This is really sick.  I think they're trying to fix us up", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Who says I want to play?  OK, what the fuck are you doing in the dumpster", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're behind the whole thing aren't you?  You and your sick fucking friends set it u", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know, out of boredom, to get back at m", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Of course, sir.  It was a white house, I remember... big tree in the front... with one of those, you know, tire swings..", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It wasn't you, sir", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend?  my frien", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You have a daughter named my friend?  I'm afraid she might be in danger", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's not his fault, he thought it was the only way out... just another victim", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Honey, they already got it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So the waitress was in on i", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "--and now you're brother's been institutionalized... is there a history of mental illness in your family", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, my friend, no, n", "docId": "Game_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You're not gonna die.  I'm here, you're not gonna die..", "qsentId": 22}]